stevens.edu 2018-09-08

# Privacy Policy | Stevens Institute of Technology

Stevens Institute of Technology is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information when you visit Stevens.edu and its digital properties, unless you voluntarily provide the information to us through email, admission applications, subscriptions and web inquiry forms. Any personal information you choose to provide us will only be used by Stevens to conduct official Stevens business. Stevens does not sell, rent, loan or trade personal information collected on this site.

When visiting Stevens.edu, we collect the following information:

  * The Internet Protocol address of the computer or mobile device that accessed Stevens.edu
  * The type of browser, its version and the operating system on which that browser is running
  * The Web page from which the user accessed the current Web page
  * The date and time of the user's request
  * The pages that were visited and the amount of time spent at each page

Stevens uses this information for internal use only for the purpose of traffic analysis, site improvement and security. This information is non-personally identifiable.

Stevens uses tools such as Google AdWords and Google Display to remarket to users who visit Stevens.edu web pages. Stevens and third party vendors, use pixel tags, small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a webpage, to obtain information about the computer being used to view a webpage, including the time spent on the site, the user’s operating system and browser type, demographic data, and similar information. These advertising tools use only non-personally identifiable information.

You may opt out of behavioral advertising by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

Stevens.edu also utilizes “cookies”, small text files placed on the user’s computer or mobile device to help track information about the user’s browsing on the site. These cookies are used to recall your personal preferences, such as usernames and passwords, or to track statistics on usage Stevens,edu and its digital properties. Stevens’ use of cookies does not involve the collection of personally identifiable information.

For information regarding the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), please click [here](https://www.stevens.edu/directory/information-technology/cyber-security-and-information-security/european-union-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-faq).
